<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Alpinas on TU4EVER</title>
    <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Alpinas on TU4EVER</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid Day 7</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day7/</guid>
      <description>July 9th, 2022 : Driving back to Jura by Gorges du Verdon Tourtour - Ste-Croix-du-Verdon - Moustiers-ste-Marie - Rougon - Castellane - Digne-les-Bains - Gap - Grenoble 📏 Distance : 430 km
⛰️ Positive elevation : 1727 m
Seventh day itinerary In order to go back to our starting point in Jura, we decided to keep driving across beautiful sceneries. Our goal was to drive through Gorges du Verdon. We kicked off in the morning near Draguignan by driving to the small village of Tourtour.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid Day 6</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day6/</guid>
      <description>July 8th, 2022 : After one week in the mountains, we reached the sea ! Via del Sale - Briga Alta - Monte Saccarello - La Brigue - Ventimiglia - Menton - Monaco - Côte d&amp;rsquo;Azur 📏 Distance : 115 km
⛰️ Positive elevation : 3937 m (while starting at 2000 m and finishing at 3 m)
Sixth day itinerary This was the last day of Alpinaraid. We went from Col de Tende to Menton city, on the border of the Mediterranean sea.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid Day 6</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day5/</guid>
      <description>July 7th, 2022 : A whole day in Italy for the second to last Alpinaraid day Colle di Sampeyre - Colle del Preit - Lago della Meja - Colle Valcavera - Colle Fauniera - Colle Esischie - Col de Tende 📏 Distance : 167 km
⛰️ Positive elevation : 5215 m
Fifth day itinerary The night at Agriturismo Lou Chirun was very relaxing, which was a very good thing for the day that was coming up.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid Day 4</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day4/</guid>
      <description>July 6th, 2022 : Sightseeing tour Rifugio Scarfiotti - Bardonecchia - Névache - Briançon - Col d&amp;rsquo;Izoard - Col Agnel - Agriturismo Lou Chirun 📏 Distance : 161 km
⛰️ Positive elevation : 6225 m
Fourth day itinerary For this fourth day of adventure, we kicked our journey off with the downhill from the Rifugio Scarfiotti to Bardonecchia.
Afterwards, we took the direction of the Vallée de Névache, by going up to the Col de L&amp;rsquo;Échelle (1762 m).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid Day 3</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day3/</guid>
      <description>July 5th, 2022 : Our 205 climbed all the way up to 3000 m ! Col Basset - Sestrières - Lago Nero - Bardonecchia - Colle del Sommeillier - Rifugio Scarfiotti 📏 Distance : 93 km (a little bit more with some detours)
⛰️ Positive elevation : 4042 m (800 m more for the bonus mountain pass)
Third day itinerary To be completely honest, day 3 itinerary read 93 km, but in reality we almost drove the double.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid Day 2</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day2/</guid>
      <description>July 4th, 2022 : Crossing the border to Italy Col du Galibier - Lac du mont Cenis - Colle del Finestre - Rifugio e colle dell&amp;rsquo;Assietta 📏 Distance : 173 km
⛰️ Positive elevation : 6241 m
Second day itinerary For this second day, a big stage is in sight. We started off with the climb of the famous Col du Lautaret (2057 m) and Col du Galibier (2642 m).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alpinaraid Day 1</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/alpina/day1/</guid>
      <description>July 3rd, 2022 : First day of the adventure Jura - Geneva - Col de la Madeleine - Lac de Grand&amp;rsquo;Maison - L&amp;rsquo;Alpe d&amp;rsquo;Huez - La Grave 📏 Distance : 148 km (+ 217 km to get to the starting point)
⛰️ Positive elevation : 4663 m (+ some bonus mountain passes to warm up)
First day itinerary On the eve of the journey, the car was loaded up with all our stuff.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
