<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>TU4EVER</title>
    <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content on TU4EVER</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>fr-fr</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Design of a custom roof rack</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/roofrack/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/roofrack/</guid>
      <description>In order to carry more stuff easily, we quickly realized that we would need to use the roof of the car. We started by buying two crossbars on the second hand market, but we knew we would need to add a roof rack to increase the usable storage area. At first, we thought we would buy a classic roof rack that could be found on the used market, but then we started looking for a custom made roofrack.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alternator replacement</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/alternator-replacement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/alternator-replacement/</guid>
      <description>In order to avoid the frequent breakdowns during the raids, we have replaced our alternator and the accessory belt. We also installed a new battery, additional cigarette lighter and USB plugs, and a voltmeter to monitor the battery voltage.
Alternator replacement Changing the alternator is a fairly simple step. We proceeded like this:
Start by disconnecting the negative (-) terminal of the battery. In our case, we have a quick disconnect, which allows us to do without wrenches for this step.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Manufacturing of bumper supports</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/bumper-supports/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/bumper-supports/</guid>
      <description>During the rebuilding of the bumpers of our Peugeot 205, we noticed that the brackets that were holding them in the back were in bad shape due to rust. Also, since we replaced the original front skirt with a Peugeot 205 GTI skirt and decided to include the long-range headlights, we had to redesign the support parts.
Of course, these parts are available for purchase and not necessarily very expensive, but on one hand we wanted to reduce the cost of the project, and on the other hand we would have the pride of making some of the parts ourselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brakes replacement</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/brakes-replacement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/brakes-replacement/</guid>
      <description>We have finally replaced the front and rear brakes of our Peugeot 205. In this article we present you an overview of the work. When we first drove our car, we immediately felt that the brakes were not in the best shape and we knew that they would have to be changed very soon. We ordered the parts and decided to do the replacement at home and without special tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Repair of 205 GTI 1.6L rims</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/wheels-restoring/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/wheels-restoring/</guid>
      <description>After we bought our Peugeot 205, we quickly had the idea to equip it with aluminum wheels. We quickly fell in love with the design of the 205 GTI rims (1.6L version). We then acquired four rims in a bad aesthetic state.
We set ourselves the goal of repairing our rims directly at home, using materials that are easily accessible for individuals. The expected result is obviously not the one we could obtain by going to a professional, or by using dedicated tools.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Renovation of the interior of the car</title>
      <link>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/interior-car-washing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sensational-crepe-a65ead.netlify.app/en/posts/interior-car-washing/</guid>
      <description>When we bought our Peugeot 205, we had to clean the interior : the seats were dirty, even stained in some places, the original color of the front carpets was starting to be questionable and the smell was not necessarily the most pleasant. So we set to work in order to feel good for the many kilometers that we will spend on board.
Here are the different steps of the cleaning.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
